Finding Aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) photograph series D (faculty and staff portraits), 1946-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Series D, Faculty and Staff Portraits
  - P
    - Pernick, Irwin, Bureau of Public Affairs, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Pernick, Martin, History, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Perring, Raymond, $55 Million Program, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Perrydore, Mary, Housing, 1990 (Box 10)
    - Person, Ruth, Library Science, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Personke, Karl, Education, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Persson, Kerstin Inez, 1950 (Box 10)
    - Peters, C. Wilbur, Physics, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Peterson, Donald C., Engineering, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Peterson, Enoch E., Kelsey Museum of Archaeology, Classical Studies, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Peterson, Frederick (Box 10)
      (na 2855)
    - Peterson, Gordon E., Electrical Engineering, 1954 (Box 10)
    - Peterson, John, Aero and Astro Engineering, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Peterson, Marvin, Center for the Study of Higher Education, 1984, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Peterson, Paul D., Engineering Mechanics, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Peterson, Shorey, Economics, 1954 (Box 10)
    - Peterson, Ward D., Bureau of Appointments and Occupational Information, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Peterson, William A., School of Business Administration, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Petoskey, E. Jack, Office of Registration and Records, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Petring, Marjorie M., Far East Languages and Literatures, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Petters, Robert, Music, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Peurasaari, Gary, WUOM, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Pew, Richard, 1967 (Box 10)
    - Pfnister, Allan O., Higher Education, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Phair, Judith, University Relations, UM News, UM Record, 1976 (Box 10)
    - Phaup, John D., Environmental Health, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Phelps, Dale E., Physical Education for Men, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Phelps, Dudley Maynard, Marketing, 1960, 1950, 1968, 1964 (Box 10)
      (nb 919-921)
    - Philipps, Joan, Women's Physical Education, 1968 (Box 10)
    - Phillies, George D. J., Chemistry, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Phillips, Betty, WUOM, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Phillips, George L., Pharmacy, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Phillips, Glen D., WUOM, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Phillips, Richard L., Aerospace Engineering, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Pick, Hans, Music, 1947 (Box 10)
      (na 2986-2987)
    - Pickens, Alexander, Art, 1956 (Box 10)
    - Pickering, Suzanne, AAUW, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Pickus, Pete, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Pickut, Alice, Food Service, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Pidd, Robert W., Physics, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Pierce, Hugh, Vocational Education and Practical Arts, 1956 (Box 10)
    - Pierce, Roy, Political Science, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Pierce, Walter B., Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Pierce, William J., Law, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Pierpont, Wilbur K., VP of the University in charge of business and finance; Accounting, 1962, 1967, 1966, 1968 (Box 10)
    - Pietras, Benjamin, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Pietras, Doris, LS&A, 1975, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Pike, Evelyn, Linguistics Department, 1976 (Box 10)
    - Pike, Kenneth L., Linguistics, 1960, 1968, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Pilcher, James C. (C. James), Finance, 1966, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Pintrich, Paul, Education, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Pippen, Richard W., Botany, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Piranian, George, Math, 1985, 1967, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Place, Irene, Office Management, 1966 (Box 10)
    - Place, Ruth Mosher, Extension Service, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Plant, Markus, Law, 1969, 1970, 1975, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Platt, John R., MHRI, 1968 (Box 10)
    - Platzman, Loren K., Industrial and Operations Engineering, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Plice, Samuel, Admin Systems, 1973, 1975, 1985, 1988 (Box 10)
    - Plotzke, Margo, Basketball, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Ploughman, Theodore L., WRL, Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Plumer, James M., Far Eastern Art, 1960 (Box 10)
      (na 2866)
    - Plummer, Robert, Flint Colelge; Education, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Poehle, Herbert F., Engineering Research Institute (Box 10)
    - Pohl, Joanne M., 1995 (Box 10)
    - Pointer, Russell A., Extension Service, 1958, 1968 (Box 10)
    - Polakowski, Kenneth J., Land Architecture, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Polasky, Alan, Law, 1976, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Polcyn, Fabian, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Politzer, Frieda N., English Language Institute, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Pollack, Peter, Land Architecture, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Pollard, H. Marvin, Internal Medicine, 1965, 1967 (Box 10)
    - Pollard, John C., Psychiatry; Mental Health Research Institute, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Pollmar, Carl, School of Business Administration, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Pollock, David S., University Relations, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Pollock, James K., Political Science, 1968 (Box 10)
    - Pomeroy, Paul, Geophysics, Geology & Mineral, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Pomey, George, Basketball, 1966 (Box 10)
    - Poole, Cecil, Law, 1976 (Box 10)
    - Pooley, Beverley C., Law, 1968, 1965, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Popelar, Carl, Engineering Mechanics, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Porcello, Leonard J., Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Port, Dr., 1954 (Box 10)
      (na 2874-2877)
    - Port, Philip Lucasse, 1954 (Box 10)
      (na 2871-2873)
    - Porter, Harry, Landscape Architecture, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Porter, James, Natural Resources, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne, 1954 (Box 10)
      (na 2878)
    - Porter, R. Clay, Mechanical Engineering, 1973, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Porter, Richard, Protozoology, 1955, 1947, 1975, 1963 (Box 10)
      (na 2051-2053)
    - Porter, William A., Electrical Engineering and Comp Engineering, 1974, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Porter, William E., Journalism, 1963, 1973, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Portman, Donald J., UMRI, Meteorology, Dept. of Civil Engineering, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Posvar, Wesley, Arms Control Symposium, 1963 (Box 10)
      (na 2055)
    - Pott, Clarence K., German, 1957, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Potter, Merle, Engineering Mechanics, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Potter, Richard L., Biological Chemistry, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Potter, Robert A., University Communication, 1979, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Potts, Philip, Engineering, 1960, 1951, 1965 (Box 11)
      (na 2056-59)
    - Powell, Don, Pyschology, 1979, 1978, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Powell, Mark W., Student, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Powell, Richard R., Law, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Powell, Thomas J., Social Work, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Power, Eugene, Regent, 1956, 1991 (Box 11)
    - Power, Sarah Goddard, Regent, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Powers, Bill, Aerospace Engineering, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Powers, Charles, Great Lakes Research Division; Zoology, 1959, 1967 (Box 11)
    - Powers, John E., Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1963, 1978, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Powers, Lyall H., English, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Poyava, Edward, 1950 (Box 11)
    - Prakken, Lawrence W., Journalism, 1953 (Box 11)
      (na 2881)
    - Pratt, David T., Mechanical Engineering, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Prentice, John T., Jr., Office of Admissions, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Preston, Stephen, Wood Technology, 1953, 1965, 1973, 1959 (Box 11)
      (na 2883)
    - Preston, William S., Bacteriology; Pasteur Institute, 1951 (Box 11)
      (nb 934)
    - Price, Allan, VP Research, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Price, Jacob M., History, 1957, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Price, Joseph, Education, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Price, Joseph, Environmental Health, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Price, Martha, Continuing Education of Women, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Price, Percival, Music, 1956, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Price, Vincent, 1988 (Box 11)
    - Price, William, Bureau of Industrial Relations, 1966, 1967 (Box 11)
    - Prince, Helen Dodson, Astronomy, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Pringle, Blanche, Admissions, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Prins, David, Speech, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Proffett, Roy Franklin, Law, 1956, 1969 (Box 11)
      (na 2884)
    - Pruitt, Aubrey, Affirmative Action, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Pryor, Frederick L., Economics, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Puff, Helmut, German, 1997 (Box 11)
    - Pugh, Mary Jo, Bentley, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Pulgram, Ernst, Romance Languages, 1951, 1980, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Pulliam, Ron, Board in Control of Intercollegiate Athletics, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Pulver, Earl B., 1961 (Box 11)
    - Purdon, T. Luther, Bureau Appt., 1953 (Box 11)
    - Putman, Lloyd, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Puto, Christopher, Marketing, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Q
    - Quackenbush, Leland J., Mechanical Engineering, 1960, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Quinn, Robert, Institute for Social Research, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Quitiquit, Ruthann, Personnel, 1974 (Box 11)
  - R
    - Raab, Ellis, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Raab, Emil, Music, 1955 (Box 11)
    - Rabe, Barry, Natural Resources, 2000 (Box 11)
    - Rabinovitch, Ralph, Education (Box 11)
      (na 2897)
    - Rabinovitz, Patricia W., Social Work, 1965 (Box 11)
      (na 2896)
    - Rabkin, Eric, 1988 (Box 11)
    - Radin, Norma, Social Work, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Radin, Norman, Mental Health Research Institute, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Radock, Helen, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Radock, Michael, VP/University Relations, 1967 (Box 11)
    - Radock, Michael and Helen, 1968, 1963, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Radock, Robert (son of Michael Radock) (Box 11)
    - Rae, James W., Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Ragone, David V., Metallurgical Engineering, 1955, 1976, 1972, 1978, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Rahv, Phillip, 1956 (Box 11)
      (na 2898)
    - Railton, Peter, Philosophy, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Ramsey, Jerome, French, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Ramsey, Robert, School of Business Administration, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Ranck, James, Physiology, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Randall, Alice (Box 11)
      (nb 935-936)
    - Randall, Harrison M., Physics, 1950 (Box 11)
      (nb 937-944)
    - Rankin, Paul, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Rao, C. S. R, Engineering Graphics, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Rapidsardi, Dana (SEE: Hopwood Winners), Hopwood Winner (Box 11)
    - Rapoport, Anatol, Mathematical Biology; Mental Health Research Institute; Psychology, 1962 (Box 11)
      (na 2899)
    - Rappaport, Roy, Anthropology, 1991, 1988, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Rassam, Hormuzd, Office of Research Administration, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Ratliff, Demetra P., 1987 (Box 11)
    - Rau, Robert, Office of Student Affairs, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Rauch, Lawrence L., Dept. of Aeronautical and Astronautical Engineering, 1960, 1964 (Box 11)
      (na 2900)
    - Ray, Dale C., Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Ray, Paul H., Urban Planning, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Raymond, William W., Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Rea, David K., Geological Sciences; Oceanography, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Rea, Walter B., Men., 1949 (Box 11)
      (na 2901)
    - Rector, Gail, University Musical Society, 1957, 1968, 1975, 1990, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Reddig, Rhoda, Nursing, 1956 (Box 11)
    - Reece, James S., Policy and Control, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Reed, Beth, Social Work, 1989, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Reed, Doris, Naval Science, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Reed, Harvey, Office of Minority Affairs, 1988 (Box 11)
    - Reed, John, Law, 1956 (Box 11)
    - Rege, Snuil Devidatta, Chemical Engineering, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Rehmus, Charles, Museums; Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations; Political Science, 1968, 1964, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Reichart, Walter A., 1950 (Box 11)
    - Reid, Pamela, Education, 1999 (Box 11)
    - Reiff, Guy Gene, Physical Education, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Reilly, Raymond R., Finance, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Reinmuth, Dennis F., Insurance, 1966, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Reiss, Albert J., Jr., Center for Research on Social Organization; Sociology, 1968, 1965, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Reister, Russell, Physical Plant, 1986, 1961, 1980, 1972, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Reitman, Walter, Psychology & Comp.; Mental Health Research Institute, 1975, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Remington, Richard, Public Health, 1963, 1979, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Remley, Fred, Michigan Media; WUOM, 1981, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Rempp, Kathy, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Renirie, Jack, News Service, 1955 (Box 11)
    - Rentschler, Gary, Education, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Reo, Gloria, Bureau of Industrial Relations, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Reskin, Barbara, Soc., 1984 (Box 11)
    - Revelli, William D., Michigan Marching Band, 1955 (Box 11)
    - Revelli, William D., University Bands; Music, 1961 (Box 11)
    - Rewoldt, Stewart H., Marketing, 1956, 1971, 1965 (Box 11)
      (na 2664-2665)
    - Reyes, Angel, Music, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Reynolds, Dick, Dearborn, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Reynolds, Frank, Public Health Administration, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Reynolds, Richard, School of Dentistry, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Reynolds, Robert, Bands, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Rhodes, Frank H. T., Academic Affairs; Geology and Mineralogy, 1974, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Rice, Louis C., 1959 (Box 11)
    - Rice, Steven, 1988 (Box 11)
    - Rice, Warner G., English, 1948, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Rich, Arthur, Physics, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Richards, Albert, Dentistry, 1956 (Box 11)
    - Richards, James W., Pharm., 1969 (Box 11)
    - Richardson, Curtis J., Natural Resources, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Richardson, Robert, News Service, 1955 (Box 11)
    - Richardson, Rudy, 1990 (Box 11)
    - Richart, Frank E., Civil Engineering, 1962, 1978, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Richburg, Keith (Box 11)
    - Richter, Glenn, Marching Band, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Ricker, Charles W., Phoenix Project, 1961 (Box 11)
    - Ricks, James D., MHRI, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Ridenour, Gerald, Public Health Engineering, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Riech, Fredric, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Riecker, John, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Riegel, John W., School of Business Administration, 1949 (Box 11)
    - Riegel, Klaus F., Psychology, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Rieke, Thomas G., DRDA, 1976, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Rigan, Dennis, Physical Education, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Riggs, Thomas R., Biological Chemistry, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Riley, Jack (Box 11)
    - Ringe, Donald A., English, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Riordan, John, Institute of Science and Technology, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Risenhoover, Morris, Music, 1983, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Riskey, Earl N., Physical Education for Men, 1953, 1957 (Box 11)
    - Ristenbatt, Marlin, Engineering, 1968, 1962, 1975, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Ritchie, William, English Language Institute, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Rivera, Rhonda, Law School (Box 11)
    - Roach, Thomas, Regent, 1975, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Roberts, Richard, Electrical Engineering, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Roberts, Thomas, Bureau of Industrial Relations, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Robertson, Andrew, Great Lakes Research Division, 1967 (Box 11)
    - Robertson, James, English, 1968, 1962, 1957 (Box 11)
      (na 2670)
    - Robeson, Kathryn, Public Health Nursing, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Robinett, Betty, 1956 (Box 11)
      (na 2671)
    - Robinovitz, Stewart, Technical Support, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Robinson, Alfred, Astronomy, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Robinson, Dave, Admissions Office, 1984, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Robinson, David II, Dearborn, 1968, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Robinson, Dorothy, Social Work, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Robinson, John, ISR, 1975, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Robinson, John P., Journalism, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Robinson, Terry, Psychology, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Robinson, William D., Internal Medicine, 1956, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Robson, John, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Roderick, Stephen A., Education, 1979, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Roe, Byron, Physics, 1977, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Roeber, Edward C., Education, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Roemele, Eugene C., Law, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Roeper, Peter, Institute of Gerontology?, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Rogers, Bryan, Art & Design, 2000 (Box 11)
    - Rogers, David C. D., School of Business Administration, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Rogers, Don E., Aeronautical Engineering, 1958 (Box 11)
    - Rogers, J. Speed, 1949 (Box 11)
      (na 2672)
    - Rogers, K. T. (Box 11)
      (na 2673)
    - Rogers, Priscilla, Business Administration, 1988 (Box 11)
    - Rogin, Lawrence, Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations, 1957 (Box 11)
      (na 2674-2677)
    - Rojnik, Albert, 1950 (Box 11)
      (na 2950-2953)
    - Rolfsen, N. Gerald, Arch. & Design, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Rolliman, Mary E., Library, 1952 (Box 11)
    - Romani, John, Public Health Administration, 1963, 1961 (Box 11)
    - Rondell, Paul, Physiology, 1966, 1964, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Root, Margaret C., Kelsey Museum, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Root, William L., Aeronautical and Astronautical Engineering, 1961 (Box 11)
    - Rose, Jerry, Hospital Administration, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Rose, Walter, Engineering, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Rosemond, Ernest, Orientation (Box 11)
    - Rosen, Stephen, Internal Medicine, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Rosenblatt, Jacqueline, 1951 (Box 11)
      (na 2954-2959)
    - Rosenstock, Irwin, Public Health Administration, 1963, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Rosenthal, Robert A., Survey Research Center, 1961 (Box 11)
      (nb 949-951)
    - Rosko, Peter, School of Business Administration, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Roslin, Carolyn M., Information and News Service, 1960 (Box 11)
      (nb 952-953)
    - Ross, Arthur, 1969, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Ross, Diane, Physical Education, 1967 (Box 11)
    - Ross, Gilbert, Music, 1966, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Ross, Ian C., Institute for Social Research, 1957 (Box 11)
      (na 2973)
    - Ross, Marc, Physics, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Ross, Richard J., English, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Rosseels, Gustave A., Music, 1969, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Roterus, Victor, 1947 (Box 11)
      (na 2974)
    - Roth, Walter M., Plant Department, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Rothe, Erich, Mathematics, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Rothfarb, Lee, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Rothman, Jack, Social Work, 1964, 1983, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Rotzel, Harold L. (Box 11)
      (Olds, Floyd)
    - Rouse, Ruth (Box 11)
      (na 2976)
    - Roush, Robert J., Cashier, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Rowe, Joseph E., Electrical Engineering, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Rowe, Kenneth, English, 1957, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Rowe, Tom D., Pharmacy, 1956, 1955 (Box 11)
    - Ruch, Walter, School of Public Health, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Rucknagle, Donald, Human Genetics, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Rudd, Dale F., Chemical Engineering, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Rugen, Mabel, Health Education, 1963, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Rulfs, Charles L., Chemistry, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Rumman, Wadi S., Civil Engineering, 1960, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Rush, Jon, Art & Design, 2000 (Box 11)
    - Rush, Pete, Higher Education, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Rush, Stephen, Dance Dept., 1987 (Box 11)
    - Ruskin, Arnold M., Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1961 (Box 11)
    - Russel, Rhoda, School of Nursing, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Russell, Alice, 1949 (Box 11)
      (na 2762-2765)
    - Russell, Rosemary, Music, 1966, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Russo, Joseph, Classical Studies, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Ruston, Henry, UMRI; Electrical Engineering, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Ruthven, Alexander G., 1949 (Box 11)
    - Ruthven, Theodore (Box 11)
    - Rutledge, Lester T., Physiology, 1965, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Ryan, Paul, Internal Audit, 1965, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Ryder, Meyer, Industrial Relations, 1966, 1954, 1955 (Box 11)
      (nb 965)
    - Rzonca, Chester S., Education, 1971 (Box 11)
  - S
    - Sadik, Server, Inst. Engineering Mechanics, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Sadler, Walter C., Civil Engineering, 1949 (Box 11)
      (na 2774-n2777)
    - Sadowsky, Thomas, Engineering Mechanics, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Sahlins, Marshall D., Anthropology, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Sain, Lenord F., School of Education, 1975, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Saint Antoine, Theodore, Law School, 1967, 1971, 1996, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Saint Clair, Carl, Conducting, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Saint Clair, Jean, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Saint Claire, Robert K., 1978 (Box 11)
    - Sakaraba, Ichiro, Electrical Engineering, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Salazar, Ignacio, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Salmon, James, Music, 1951, 1960, 1954 (Box 11)
      (na 2778-2781)
    - Salomon, Gavriel, Education Psychology, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Salvesen, Nils, Naval Arch., 1964 (Box 11)
    - Samanta, Shyam K., Mechanical Engineering, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Sample, Shirley L., Personnel, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Samuelson, Charles H., Naval Science, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Samuelson, Mary H., Michigan Student Assembly, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Sanders, Walter, 1950 (Box 11)
    - Sandman, Peter, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Sandor, Gyorgy, Music, 1961, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Sandstrom, Robert E., 1980 (Box 11)
    - Sapolsky, Harvey, Institute of Public Policies Studies, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Sarri, Rosemary, Social Work, 1973, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Sarris, Geroge R., Extension Service, Dearborn, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Satake, Kenzi, Geology, 1990 (Box 11)
    - Sattler, William M., Speech, 1957 (Box 11)
    - Sauer, Charles, English Language Institute, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Saunders, George W., Zoology, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Sauve, Robert P., VP Academic Affairs, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Savage, Phillip, Chemical Engineering, 1987, 1996 (Box 11)
    - Saville, Dudley, Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Sawyer, Charles H., Museum of Art, Architecture and Design, LS&A, 1958, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Sawyer, Ralph, VP Research; Physics, 1967, 1963, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Sawyer, Thomas M., Jr., Engineering, 1963, 1980, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Sax, Joseph, Law, 1967, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Saxonhouse, Arlene, 1993 (Box 11)
    - Saxonhouse, Gary R., Economics, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Sayers, Tom, UMTRI, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Sayler, Richrd, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Scanlan, Eleanore, BIR, 1967 (Box 11)
    - Scearse, Patricia, Nursing, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Schaadt, Leonard A., Residence Halls, 1962, 1951 (Box 11)
      (na 2783-2786)
    - Schaefer, Hadley, Dearborn, 1967 (Box 11)
    - Schauer, Frederick F., Law, 1986 (Box 11)
    - Scheele, Robert F., Landscape Architecture, 1978, 1974, 1982 (Box 11)
    - Scheeledes, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Scheeres, Daniel, Engineering, 1999 (Box 11)
    - Schellie, Peter D. (Box 11)
    - Schelske, C. L., Great Lakes Res. Division, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Scherrer, Mike, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Schiller, Nan, 1955 (Box 11)
      (na 2787)
    - Schilt, Alfred A., Chemistry, 1960 (Box 11)
    - Schindler, J. S., Business Administration, 1955 (Box 11)
    - Schlatter, William J., School of Business Administration, 1960, 1951, 1967 (Box 12)
      (na 2788)
    - Schleh, Dan, Housing, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Schlesinger, Lawrence E., Research Center for Group Dynamics; Institute for Social Research, 1959 (Box 12)
    - Schlitt, Anne, WUOM, 1977 (Box 12)
    - Schlussel, Debbie, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Schmale, Herbert T., Psych., 1951 (Box 12)
    - Schmidt, Brian B., Hebrew, 1996 (Box 12)
    - Schmidt, Courtland, Surgery (Box 12)
    - Schmidt, Leo, School of Business Administration, 1966, 1961, 1960, 1952 (Box 12)
      (nb 966-968, na 2789)
    - Schmiedeskamp, Jay, ISR, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Schmuck, Richard, Psychology, ISR, 1965 (Box 12)
    - Schmult, Carl, Architecture, 1965 (Box 12)
    - Schneidewind, Richard, Metallurgical Engineering, 1960 (Box 12)
    - Schnell, Kemph, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Schnitzer, Mr. And Mrs. Robert C., 1961 (Box 12)
    - Schnitzer, Mrs. Robert C., 1961 (Box 12)
    - Schnitzer, Robert C., Speech, 1961 (Box 12)
    - Schnitzer, Robert C., Mrs. (SEE: Cisney, Marcella) (Box 12)
    - Schnitzer, Thomas J., Public Health, 1981 (Box 12)
    - Schoch, Peter F., Housing, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Schock, Michael, Biostatistics, 1963 (Box 12)
    - Schoderbek, Peter P., School of Business Administration, 1960 (Box 12)
    - Schoem, David, Sociology (Box 12)
    - Schoen, Valerie, 1972 (Box 12)
    - Schoenfeldt, Michael, English, 1985 (Box 12)
    - Schoffer, Ivo, History, 1966 (Box 12)
    - Scholl, Geraldine T., Education, 1964, 1973, 1982, 1961 (Box 12)
    - Scholler, Harald, German, 1965 (Box 12)
    - Schooler, Kermit, 1956 (Box 12)
      (na 2792)
    - Schorger, William D., Anthropology, Near Eastern Studies, 1960 (Box 12)
    - Schrader, Albert W., Bureau of Industrial Relations, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Schramm, Gunter, School of Natural Resources, 1970 (Box 12)
    - Schriber, Thomas J., Business Administration, 1973, 1966, 1970 (Box 12)
    - Schrier, Harvey, 1951 (Box 12)